

Contacts

☐ Phone

964815670

☑ Email

vladvaz@gmail.com

Q Location

Castelo Branco, PT

in LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/vladimiro-vaz

GitHub

github.com/vladvaz

Skills

Angular C C# F# HTML Java **Ocaml PostgreSQL**

React **SASS**

Typescript

Scala

Python

VLADIMIRO JOÃO DOS SANTOS VAZ

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

PROFILE

Computer engineer with over 3 years of experience in developing reactive front-end applications using Angular and React. Experience with Rest APIs and micro services. Accustomed to working in an agile environment and using a TDD approach. Curious to learn new technologies and methodologies.

EXPERIENCE

Full-stack developer

Devoteam

December 2021 - Present

- Migration and improvement of an existing web application, used by employees and customers of a swiss insurance company.
- Creation of new pages, following the rules defined by the design team;
- Integration with the backend services;
- Creation of npm libraries to interact with several microservices;
- Migration and updating of old pages with new features;
- Bug fixes and code reviews;
- Technical debt reduction;
- Creation of unit tests and documentation.

Angular Typescript Ngxs Rxjs Jasmine SASS C# .Net

Front-end developer

Capgemini Engineering

August 2019 - December 2021

- Development of a music player for infotainment systems in vehicles, using web technologies.
- Creation of new pages, following the rules defined by the design team;
- Creating transitions and micro-interactions on pages;
- Integration with backend services;
- Creation of unit tests and documentation.

Angular Typescript Rxjs Jasmine SASS Nest.js

Languages

Portuguese - C2

English - C1

French - A2

Hobbies

Game development

Watch movies

Playing guitar

Go to the gym

Full-stack developer

Capgemini Engineering

October 2020 - January 2021

- Development of a responsive web application for managing employees and their respective projects.
- Web application creation;
- Creating new components in React;
- Defining style sheets with SASS;
- Creating and managing the global state of the application using the Redux library;
- Creating and validating forms;
- Development of backend services;
- Creating a REST API using Express and Node.js;
- Creation and maintenance of a database using MySQL;
- Creating unit tests and documentation.

React React Redux React Router React Hook Form TypeScript Jest
Node.js MySQL SASS

EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science

Universidade da Beira Interior - FE

2016 - 2019

Master's Degree in Civil Engineering

Universidade de Coimbra - FCTUC

2007 - 2013

CERTIFICATES

Machine Learning with Python

Coursera 2021/12/20

www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/certificate/W8QGP7J9KJ8J

Big Data Analysis with Scala and Spark

Coursera 2021/07/12

www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/certificate/YZ2EJYPWA869

Functional Programming Principles in Scala

Coursera 2021/06/08

www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/certificate/67R2MKQGZDTQ